inspirationsandinnovations.com 2013-04-19

# World of Inspirations and Innovations!!!

**Privacy Policy for** **inspirationsandinnovations.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@inspirationsandinnovations.com. 

At **inspirationsandinnovations.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by inspirationsandinnovations.com and how it is used. 

This privacy policy sets out how  **inspirationsandinnovations.com** uses and protects any information that you give  **inspirationsandinnovations.com** when you use this website or application. **

inspirationsandinnovations.com

** is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website or application, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  **

inspirationsandinnovations.com

** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from December 1, 2011.

**What we collect** We may collect the following information: contact information including name, email address, demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests, other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers and according to Facebook permissions granted by any user of the Inspirations and Innovations application.

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping, improve our products and services, send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information, contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website or application according to your interests. We also use your Facebook credentials to connect you with the website or application and track your membership accessibility.

**Security** We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we are using standards deemed safe by Facebook, suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies  
**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website and or application.

**Links to other websites  
**  
Our website or application may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over any other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information  
**  
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [ admin@inspirationsandinnovations.com](mailto:admin@inspirationsandinnovations.com).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Log Files**    
  
Like many other Web sites,  **inspirationsandinnovations.com** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**    
  
**inspirationsandinnovations.com** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**    
  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  inspirationsandinnovations.com.   
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to inspirationsandinnovations.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
Google Adsense   
Lifestreet Media International

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on inspirationsandinnovations.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

**inspirationsandinnovations.com** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. inspirationsandinnovations.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
